Um uh
uh
hello
um uh
food flying hello
uh hyung Vivian
hello Keiko hello nice to meet you there are
still
people who haven't come in [music] I'll
come a little more almost work I have
n't been able to put the answer on that plate
and also
Philtong shiver and also victory and
new year nice to meet you I'll come with some
uh
um something didn't go well this
this
this this
with that pressure originally slow cogoro
was going to run for a little longer but since I had to do it
lotto tight and
North Korea 06:00
ah give me 6 hours so around 5 5 o'clock
I left it on for 30 minutes with pressure and went to
check the gold but it kept
coming out and it happened when I
just checked and
there was a c7 error code so what's wrong I
opened the lid of Heo-eon Khan and thought it was because it was
hot I took it out and it was
warm but it doesn't
seem to be enough I looked for the code with the body like this and it seems like the
pressure
vent isn't closed or the silver is
n't heating or there's a lack of moisture or  Well,
it doesn't seem to be lacking moisture,
and since it's not a Mulim, it
seems like it might have been opened and used after the pressure cabbage was opened, but maybe it was open.
Anyway, it does
n't seem to be fully cooked
yet. So I pressed it for 15 minutes and
came back,
but I
couldn't not eat it, so I
brought one. It's
still a bit undercooked, but
I read it, but I don't think I read it.
Well, if you eat one more and it's
full, there will be another.
This bike line is worth it and
it's similar.
Hello, Okrim Mannarini, who called Bitnim, Malrang Min 8, Baekrim Kang Saeng-nim,
nice to meet you.
4 And this
time, Friday, today is my grandmother's 80th
birthday,
so of course
it would be best to go and come back on the day, but since I
can't bloom Aries as I please,
what kind of person said that if it's my second son, I
should go down to me, so the professor
left and I was
thinking about what to do, and I
took him on Friday. So I
went and came back on Friday. I should have become a grandmother.
Now, on Friday, I chose grandmother, and
even then, I almost caught one and celebrated my
grandmother's birthday.  As a gift, I
gave her some chestnuts and breast milk fever and such.
Yes, at
that time, Grandma Mo gave me chestnuts
and I
was going to talk about the two Koreas, but I
didn't have any. Now, she's still taking pictures of the chestnuts, so I
took this bag of chestnuts and the ones that raised my dreams, and I also brought sweet potatoes like this. I kept saying that I could do
anything, but she kept telling me to take them, so I put them in
when I cook rice and she said something. I
brought them. I was wondering what to do with them, and I
thought I could just turn them around while I was making lamb, so I
put a lot of noodles in them.
Yes, I thought that if I did
n't put something in them, they wouldn't eat and
would break them, so I
put a lot of whatever I put in and
did it with me
instead of the front.
Hello, Major. The chestnuts are cooked. Oh, wait a minute. I caught a few. I took some pictures while looking at them. Oh, Lee Soo-min, construction meme. Hello, I didn't. That Izumi, girlfriend, Haru. Hello,
Mr. Oh, hello.
Who is it around this time?
But this is half delicious. It's
almost pickled in oil and such.
2.
4.
We  There's a lot of oil.
Of course, what I'm eating right now
doesn't have much effect, but it's really dry and I
need to tell you about the website.
Hello, Mr. Bang Young-min. Are you Miss Leez?
If you don't know what another c boyfriend is,
what should I do?
Ah, this is because the
calves have just been born at the ranch these days, and they
were born last
night. Oh, my calf was born too, so the calf is cute, but I keep getting busy and doing this. This one was born last night, and because it's
getting busy,
I can't eat right away by myself. The milk is
too big, so it keeps getting like this in the middle,
so I have to
find it with my hand and hold it like this and
repeat it several times.
Ji-ae is getting the hang of it now, and that's also part of it, so anyway, I feel like a stepmother. Ugh, I
think four of them have gone bad so far. It hasn't even been a week.
And almost all of them are winter. I
took pictures, but I
don't think you need to show them. Um, I
think a perilla seed has come in once.
Oh, a goby or a badger or something
came in and
attacked us on the street.  It's not the same. It does
n't seem like it was a horse that had been handled so many times. It probably looks like
the raccoons and the raccoons
don't move in groups because they're so noisy and sticky,
so I think a group came in like this. They came and
caused a ruckus, and they
caught and ate one on the spot,
and almost one duck each, and
bit the rest,
killing them or
leaving wounds and breaking their legs.
You haven't even identified the culprit yet.
So they almost climbed up to the top
and said something was over the mountain and
that they would come looking for them later.
Anyway, only a few died right away. I
thought the ones bitten would be cured, but
as we live, when we get hurt, we
roll up
like this and scab over and heal, right? And goats,
of course, not just the kids, but the older
ones also get hurt. It's a business standard.
But when they do, they disinfect things, and even if they do
n't disinfect well, they know how to get
better. It's the same with cows. I
don't know if it's just how it is. Oh, it's the same with
us. When we get hurt, we roll up like this and scab over.
The fly lays eggs, and maggots bloom and
eat everything inside the body and it
dies.
So,
two more of them died, and we also
died a few more.
So, I was thinking of catching
one for my grandmother's birthday, and
that's when the
incident happened.
So,
as a birthday present for my grandmother, I
caught the biggest one, and then I
spread it like this, and
when I went to see it,
it had permed its wings and died. One of the ones that had its wings
stuck had been kicked by a maggot, and it
looked like it would be dead when I came back the next day. So I
thought, "This kid can't do it," and I caught it. The biggest one
had been bitten all over its body, so I
think I caught it well. The next day, I went back and saw that the
one that looked fine on the outside was
giving it too much and stuff.
Andy's equal, the
wings were hot,
so he caught one and gave me one half. He's
finished with the rest, so I split it in half and
tried to grill it and eat it, the
leg part.  Half of it, ah, this is
what I caught.
This was given to me as a birthday present for my grandmother, but
this one is much bigger.
Yes, this one here, this one, this one, it's all
bitten. Instead of
reacting like this,
I divided it like this and
boiled the upper part like this, and I'm going to cook the lower part
later and eat it.
Yeah, anyway, I caught it like this and
removed it first. I noticed that I was eating it right now,
so I tore it apart and caught the one that got eaten. But
it's like a small intestine, so it's dried up and floating. It does
n't have any arms and even
if you say it's almost like that, follow me. If you
look closely, you'll see that it must have taken some fat. If you look at this one, it
doesn't have much chest fat. It doesn't have
any eyes for a day. It's almost like a full stomach. I thought, "What should I eat?" I did it. 5 pieces of goby are okay, but it seems like it can't gain weight. Anyway, the ones I ate did
n't have much fat. Anyway, this one, this one, this one, the
biggest one
had a lot of fat.
I was surprised when I caught it and
cut open its belly to take out the store here, and the fat was gushing out.
Ah, I
cut open 4 bells and the fat was like some kind of revenge.  Here it is. There is
a lot of visceral fat. It's
so shocking.
Wow, this is also
the name of the chicken. In the stomach, the guest, this is just
oily. It's a lot of oil here too. The
bottom is shiny and it
came out firmly. It's amazing.
And when you
eat intestines, it's like a new car
full of oil, but did
you know that it's actually upside down?
Large intestines originally have
sugar and fat on the outside, so when you flip it over, the
fat goes in and the intestines
come out, right? This one is the
same. Like the five large intestines, there's a lot of
fat stuck to the outside of the intestines. So I
scraped it all off, but I
didn't scrape off all the visceral fat. It was
a bit difficult to scrape off everything, so I just did the
large ones that were visible, but
this much
came out. The reason the pan was dirty was because I don't wash the dishes often. So
there was a really huge amount of oil. It was almost like I could fry chicken. I was
reckless and grilled meat here and put
eggs.  I ate fried eggs and
almost blew myself up. There's still
a lot of apple juice left. I need to eat it,
but today, please do something.
This is Baeksu Kang.
Aya, the winner, my
friend,
the little one, took a picture in the middle of Eojindong.
In our country, most people who raise them
eat them, so there's not much to sell or anything like that.
222 I'm a
little worried. Should I call it tendon?
2. It doesn't seem to be. It's long, so
there's
a lot. So, as a recommendation, I went to Pitan Bibe and piled it up, but if you eat that black, it'll be
like Trump and a wish. Are you talking about Vitamin B Vega or Smoby One? I don't think I've heard that most Vitamin E is good for smoking, but B1 can cause some dizziness. Uh, and taking magnesium together
can help. Let
me tell you, I forgot, but
Elliot 5 Button emphasized that
a lot.
When taking thiamine megabus B1 megadoses, it's good to take magnesium together.
Yes, so if you're not drinking magnesium water,
It's good to drink some strength. It's a
key ingredient in B1 soup. Magnesium is
used a lot as a cofactor. This
2nd
Baekhyun, hello. If
you drink it at night,
how much is it? Hello, Mint Chim, who is obsessed with evil. Hey, Ori and I think it's a little better than us. I do
n't eat a lot of lyrics and
eat mostly grass, so I
don't know exactly, but I do
n't think I have that much six.
There must be quite a bit of Omega 3, because I eat a lot of grass.
But now, just
where is it in this form? If not, it
's probably in the form of alpha-linolenic acid.
Yes, that's probably the most abundant.
Oleic acid is the first oleic acid. Omega 3 is the main nutrient. It's
already young. Olive oil has a lot of
it. Now, there's a lot of it.
And there will be some fat. It'll be
slightly warm at room temperature.
Um, the field has
5 types of
fat. It's a little similar to the situation.
If you look at how easily it melts, it's saturated fat.
And since I don't eat any feed at all, there must
be some linoleic acid.
Can I brush my baby's teeth with Corina Clay for the first time?
Play.  Among carcinogens, the story of the North Korean army was
later fought, so everyone knows, but will it
get warmer?
Yes, I think it's okay even if you take the shape of the first alley.
But actually, you can just use toothbrush gel.
Just salt, soak
it in salt water, and then this clan cat grotesque. Now, it's better to use a clean one. Most of the ones for food use have been tested, so I thought you'd know, but just in case, it's best to eat anything that's not the same name. Even if it's for drinking, if you
want to be more sure, it's
good to ask the manufacturer if they've tested the heavy metal levels. Just like this,
heavy metals have the property of attracting neutrality in our bodies.
So, it's possible that they've already been absorbed by heavy metals before we eat them.
But even if it enters our bodies, the
absorbed heavy metals wo
n't be released back into our bodies like this, so I
don't think it's a big problem. But
just in case, you don't know, and you're a little uneasy, you
can use this.
After that, clay might come out of places like Per von Ya.  There's no such
thing as clay double-stone, so even if you do
n't have it, California can pronounce anything and that's why
there's something like that now.
If you have it, it's a bit
late for a few weeks
because there's a phenomenon of a farmer's relationship with a famous saying. What should I do? I don't think it's pretty.
Try reducing this amount and taking it little by little. Hello, Mr. Le. If you stop taking it, won't you feel gas? Can you take it after taking it after
taking it for a while? Will intravenous vitamin C help when you have low stamina?
No.
Is intravenous vitamin C related to pine trees? 4
Yes, so vitamin C is
low stamina, but first of all, taking the twisted seed
itself is a little bit. 2
So now
[music]
Next, C is an antioxidant, right? If you have
low stamina, water. Now, what's the scent?
And
when there's something that can't be resolved with oxidative stress, becoming an instructor, what
kind of CTD is it? But in that case, I
saw a good glutathione injection.
If you really want to take an anti-oxidant externally, I
saw a clotting injection. Is there a price difference?
Well, the other message will be cheaper.
Yes, anyway,
taking that much C is not at
all.  It's not natural and it's not good for your body.
Hello, Naniwa. I
just eat LDPC with fat, so it
seems to be high in fat and high in protein. Would intermittent fasting
be helpful? If you look at it, to prevent protein overload,
protein overload occurs
when you don't eat fat and make protein.
Protein overload
can never occur if you eat a lot of fat and meat. It's
not absolute, but if you eat 3kg of culture at a time, it
might be a bit much, but if it's not that much, you
don't have to worry about it.
It's good to always fast.
And I don't
know how much you eat, but it's
unlikely to be 300.
I feel like you're smoking a moderate amount.
Most people do that.
What do you mean by eating a lot while eating the right amount? Of course, you're
using more than you usually do, so
if you eat meat every day, you might think you're
eating a lot compared to what you usually eat, but it's
better to eat that amount.
Then,
first of all, it seems like there's a deficiency.
What are the symptoms of a deficiency?  If you can feel it,
one of the most common things is that
when you eat carbohydrates, your body
can feel really bad. It's essential for carbohydrate
metabolism. If you
eat a lot of carbohydrates and don't eat meat like most people do, your
body will continue to consume a lot of thiamine.
Without it, you can
easily develop a deficiency.
Yes, there's that too. If your energy metabolism
isn't working well, you're feeling weak, and you're always feeling
weak, it's said that
doti can help.
Chairman is also essential for digestion, so if you have
poor digestion or
can't digest anything like HCL in Seoul,
thiamine
can be helpful.
It's also related to diseases related to July and diabetes, which can cause blood sugar problems. I've
tried various things, but
nothing seems to work. My cardiovascular disease
risk indicators keep rising,
or my
diabetes risk keeps rising, and I've tried
reducing my carbohydrate intake. In those cases,
looking at a megadose of solar energy
can be helpful. The
nervous system is also affected.
There are people with autonomic nervous system disorder,
or if the move lamp is severe, it
can also apply, and
concentration is low. Now, that
part is also filled with t-am. Try the effect yourself. If you do net, you can
see the effect with megadosed tree tea. If you do it with just outerwear, you can't see the effect. It
's better to take it in the form of ttf.
Uzo and
ah,
we can see no $1.
4. Applying long-lasting oil and
taking oregano
can also help. Now, it's not just on the toes or the feet,
but there's a
high probability that it's inside the body, so I don't think alkaline water is
very good.
Of course, even if it's alkaline water, it
doesn't have much alkaline content, but it's just
water and * It's not like that, but
it's good for us to always be acidic, and it's
not good to get alkaline water on top of that.
Children, if it's cooled appropriately, I
don't think it's necessary, but
if you can eat enough within that time, you can do it, but
if you can't eat enough within that time, it's better not to do it.
Intermittent fasting health
18 to 6 like this 6-hour
compression or 20s social family
4-hour compression and things like that I do
n't really want to recommend, but
16s Paris or
at least 11 to 22, it's not good to eat as soon as you wake up
because there are few seeds like that in the fall, so it's
good to eat before going to bed. It's
better to have a set schedule.
As for snacks, it's better to not eat too much, and it
's good to always eat regularly, and
it's good to eat
a lot at that time. And it's good to have some time for fasting.
I don't recommend 18 to 6, but
16s arms or 14 to
12, even if it's more loose, to
some extent. Did you know
anyone? I don't
know much about
hallux valgus. I don't know if it can be corrected with chiropractic or something.
I don't know the document well.
If
it's 100g of protein and 100g of fat, it's
roughly when you calculate only calories.
It's 1300 calories,
so if
you eat 100g of protein and 100g of fat, you're really fasting. You
're eating a
low-calorie diet and a travel-related diet. Even if you eat
100g of protein and 200g of fat, you're
now somewhat like a person.
4 If you increase it to 150g of protein and 150g of fat, you're
really making yourself like a person. Yes,
now 150g of protein and 150g of fat is
600 calories and
1350 calories, right? It's just a specific amount.
4 If you're
over 15kg, you
should eat more than 100g of protein.
Bye, and
without the 4th of the seed, the last fight and
sister, fatty liver disease is
gradually increasing. Children are like that too.
Give it to them
at 1pm and eat it
late at night, 7 or 9pm. Especially
these days, the sun doesn't set. It
would have already been given by 7pm, but
after the sun sets, it's almost 9pm.  When you go to the answer
*, first of all, it's
not good to check the mealtime for the child. Eating late at that time is
not good either.
Eating at this time is
bad, and if you eat at this time, the
body needs to be diligent, and melatonin
cannot be high like this.
Then, if he eats at night and
insulin is high, he can't sleep. If he
eats right when melatonin is already released and insulin isn't released well,
then the
blood sugar level is high and it doesn't go down, and a
lot of fatty acids are circulating in the body.
Now, it
becomes like this. It's not good for the body,
so it would be better if you pushed the 44-hour meal a little bit closer to the
children.
09:00 might be a bit too much, and
of course, it's the end time, so I
'll start a little earlier, but it would be
better if you gave it a little earlier.
If you think the amount you eat by 1 p.m. is enough, it should
n't be a big problem, but you
might be a little hungry in the morning.
Rather than breakfast, it's
around 11 a.m., so it's very  Aren't you hungry? If you
eat then, the kids aren't hungry, they're
full of energy, and their
condition is good. If they're
eating well,
then it should be okay. If
not, it would be
good to take a lot of silver.
I'll give it to you. Is
there an industrial product for Connie Search Vitamin D Kate in liquid form when you open and finish it?
Since it's MCT 5 days, I
think it's probably known as PT Wool. It might not be good to
take it for too long. MCT oil isn't that vulnerable to acidity. It's just the upper class. I don't think you have anything to worry about. Well, this HT doesn't say anything like this in the refrigerator. If it's not like that, you can store it in the refrigerator. It's
better to keep it in a slightly lower temperature for 2 hours.
Hello, I'll just briefly finish.
Half of the universe. But now, the
Bible and lifestyle habits and such are probably related.
If you haven't progressed yet, it would be
good to pay attention to ice distance, spit feet, and things like that.
Cheeks are abundant in meat, but
now my body has already completed what it lacks.
When there's a deficiency, it's difficult to correct with food. It's
absorbed through diffusion in our intestines, so even if you
eat a lot, not much is absorbed. When
we eat the general form of thiamine, it's like
this.
So, if it's been caught for a long time, it's like
thiamine in food or a general
supplement. Even if you can't
eat it, the amount that can be absorbed in our intestines is
limited, so it's
absorbed as much as possible.
It's like malic thiamine in the form of tt that can be used as a supplement.
Now,
there are things that are recommended for consumption. So, are
all of our intestines okay? Well, it depends
on what's okay, but the
type of intestinal bacteria
will naturally help when using the process.
Eating when you're healthy isn't good. Since you have athlete's foot, I think it might be a
good idea to try it. I'm eating
a lot of food, and is it right? Is
collagen good for you? I'm eating well,
but is there any other food that's good for you? I'm eating a lot of collagen, but I'm
eating it diligently. It's better to eat it in April. It's
thick and thick, and it's
called collagen.  If you do, you're probably
talking about pork rinds, chicken feet, or something like
that. 4 You should eat things like that. Clean
is
voting 5.
Connective tissue
cliffs are
restless, so
skin is 8-9. There's a lot of hair and hair,
right? Hello, Minju. [Music] Those who are under 50kg and those who are 45kg should eat about 100g of protein. Now, if you eat that much, you can get the amount of protein our body needs. Yes, that doesn't mean eating more is bad.
Umi go. What's the big deal? If you're
hungry and don't necessarily want to eat more meat, you should eat more
fat.
Hello, I can't ride this time.
The files between the kids
don't fall off very well.
That's because the crab isn't cooked well. 2.
First of all, I can't see the police. I think it's
done because I turned it briefly in the back. Oh, it does
n't fall off well. It's
safe to eat it cooked.
After all, around the
age of seven,
genetics are high, so
now
husbands and wives eat like this, so their
jaws and things like that are sugary.
So, the three generations and such thing
don't seem very convincing. I'll
pursue that lifestyle habit
from now on. Most of us who walk with a needle and a needle
say that we eat well.
I'll
do the same from now on. My gait is all wrong. Most people
walk better than average. If you
correct your gait and
pay close attention, you'll
see a lot of silver plating. The
shell is
really something.
There's a lot of collagen, like
Mentor or the phone or
meat protein clothes. It's all a lie, so you
really don't have to worry about that at all.
I've only explained a lot about that, but
now I'll just tell you the bottom line. Is
that nonsense?
Hello.
Eating protein every day together with other things
can have a bit of an effect, but eating
a lot of meat and fat, like Rem Tor
and Ponyo on the island, is nonsense.
Especially, if you
say you have a high-protein diet, you're not
going to eat it all the time. By no means, if you
eat it regularly, it becomes
more intense and you catch more. It
stimulates the
4th generation.  Here,
n Thor does
n't need the right amount of gi, but it's an
example.
There are four walking chopsticks in the ear canal, right? They're really
bold and hollow, and if they're like that, the
body muscles and stuff
won't be able to maintain the body. Mentor.
Now that I look at it, how much is needed to
maintain my health?
When drinking water, is it
severe to learn?
Cooking 9, Yangsaeng, Goryeo, is there a difference like a test version? Um, if you boil it, it's like copper. Of course, which material is copper? It has a lot of oil.
In season 9, it's like regular copper. In
that case, there
may be some difference in
vitamin D intake. But the oyster itself is
n't a food that's made like that. But
now, it contains a lot of 24, which is difficult for us to eat in general. In
particular, it contains a lot of copper and zinc.
Minerals like copper and zinc are
not destroyed when cooked,
but they can flow out.
Especially, if you boil it, the horns
are diluted, and of course, this
comes out. Boiled water,
steamed, opened
underneath.  Of course, it
will drip out of the water, and if you put it on an oyster shell like this, and just
drink the broth that comes out of it, you
can eat it all.
Even if it's a rice cotton swab, you can drink all the water
and be satisfied.
There will be a certain amount of filler coming out like this, but you have to
adjust the amount to a deficit, or
not cook it for too long.
We're not going to
boil oysters for hours like we do, right?
Even if you cook them, it'll only be for a
short time, so I do
n't think you have to worry about it being too moist.
It's 4th grade. You
can just drink the water that comes out of the pan while defrosting. Gobi is
eaten raw, and
if
you didn't eat it, the blood would
have been
in it anyway, right? It comes out while it was being cooked, so
it's the same. 4. Yes,
since it's the water inside,
if you can eat the meat raw, you
can eat the water inside raw.
Of course, if you eat it, you have to take further measures. After all,
that's the water that comes out, right? I think it's because you boiled it earlier.
As I mentioned, minerals and vitamins are lost through
water. When you drink water,
vitamins and minerals are not released. However,
since they flow out, water-soluble vitamins are released to
some extent. On this day, they all came out, so of
course, dad also came out, but
there is some loss. In that process,
too, when you grill meat, the
meat juices leak out like this and
stick to it, right? Yes, that's B.
Tom's male vitamin, minerals, and things like that.
Now, when you drink water, as the meat juices leak
out,
there is a little bit of loss.
Also, hello, Mr. Moon.
To get the maximum amount of nutrients at the same price, it's
better to drink a lot.
When we celebrate, we also
buy blood in a hurry. Now,
strictly speaking, when you mix meat or liver or something like that, it's
not blood.
It's a mixture of mioglobin and water.
4. To be more intuitive,
of course, there are many more wild things in regular blood.
Ali Kami.  If I'm going to eat it, would Tia Ment
be okay?
But
TRX is a little more
4.
Oh, and of course, they say it's clean, but
Elio Burton, who advertises TMX,
says it's a little cleaner, but that's what
Ikea Mi is in.
One Star Eight is organized, but money is a little bit. What about the
stereo officetel's eat? Is
that an excipient or something like that? It
makes the amount by filling it by piercing it and adding
more like this
?
Originally, let's put 100mg of nutrients into the capsule, right? What about magnesium 1, the lower part of the town? Then, when you put 5 in one, there's not an appropriate amount of filler, and it's difficult to put the exact amount into all the capsules.
So, if the kid is 4, it's a little
straight, or if it's often starch, let's put more corn experts. Now, they say that all of that goes in to make it easy to put it in by measuring the exact amount well.
Why are you saying that Street is not that bad as a goal, but it's just a
two-layer thing that combines stearic acid and magnesium.
So, it's not really that bad.  It's not like it's dirtier
or MX is cleaner than TX,
but anyway,
TRX has minimized the presence of such nutrients, and on the
other hand, it contains a
small amount in the form of a rat test.
Then, when
I vomit again, if there's a lot, I
tell them to eat it together, so they
put in a little magnesium.
But anyway, TMS is also good. While
doing classic, I didn't eat any vegetables, and I ate as much as I wanted with
the National Assembly and liver, and ate 1 or 2 tablespoons of raw bones, and my
condition improved. My
legs don't hurt either.
But my fasting blood sugar in the morning
is much higher than when I vomited. Is it
because of the honey? My fasting blood sugar was originally low, but it's going up
to 90.
And when I drink the same alcohol as before, my
blood sugar sometimes doesn't go down for 3 hours. Is
it because of the delayed effort? Oh, if your fasting blood sugar was low, but now it's going up to 90, that means you'll be in your 80s for the rest of your life. I don't think you have much to worry about in your 80s.
If you eat a lot of meat, your
blood sugar can rise a little more. Eat
more meat.  Since you use it, your daily wage may increase a bit,
so I don't think you need to worry about it
coming out until 9 o'clock.
But are you eating it?
Answer 1. It
doesn't mean that the issue will be resolved and achieved.
Before, I
used to check my blood sugar level separately when I used it because I was busy, but now it's
not dropping. What is it? They
say that salvation is called mountain oyster. Is it really that good for stamina? It
seems
a bit excessive. Um, it's called that because it has 4.2 in the nutritional content.
Both have a lot of iron. Wow,
4.
I don't know exactly what the other nutrients are, but I
know that it has a lot of zinc.
And now,
oh, it's good for the spirit, but
since it's called oyster,
oyster would be good too.
Rather than thinking of it as something like, "Ohhan is
similar to oyster in terms of nutrients, so it's called that," it would be
more correct to think of it as being named that way.
In any case,
zinc is a very essential nutrient
for sexual function for both men and women, so
it's not an unheard of story.
I eat it every day.  I'm eating 100 micro-fine particles,
eating a lot of fat, and getting enough protein.
I think the cooking ratio is about 3343 to 43. It
seems to be a shellfish restaurant. Is there anything I should be careful of?
Exercise strategy: I exercise for about an hour a day.
When is your condition good?
First of all, if you're in good condition, I
think it would be good to get a test that can show insulin sensitivity once in a while. Rather
than anything else, just
searching for slim on an empty stomach once in a while would be enough.
Of course, now,
when talking about the land cycle, many people say that it's better to always eat when metabolizing 3, and
when living in a rural area, it's better to eat
less, and eating both together is not good for the body.
But there are many people in traditional groups who just suffered. It was the same in
Wen Tal and Masai.
There are many people who don't care much about that, so I do
n't think there's a need to worry too much.
But now, you
can check fasting insulin once in a while. When I was
playing with my character's nickname this year, I
noticed that if I drink alcohol, I
seem to have a persistent problem. The accumulated shilling of fasting insulin is
sometimes low.  Is that right?
Oh, yeah, is it 2C that you can see? In
this case, I need to eat 3 carbonated drinks to prevent
this sincerity. I'm
confused. Raw fish helps with leg cramps, so I
'm eating some more.
If you fast for 2 days, it
means that your insulin is very sensitive.
So, sincerity is far from this. But if you
continue to eat rice without carbohydrates
for a long time, the body's physiological
insulin theory is created. So, this
insulin resistance is
inside.
It's not a good story to lump everything together. The terminology is a bit
strange.
Anyway,
by eating a carbohydrate meal, my
ground is a little high, and my normal fasting
blood sugar is
ah, or suddenly I ate elasticity. My
blood sugar doesn't drop well. Our
body doesn't normally use carbohydrates at all, and
I only use it.
As a person,
there are cells that we absolutely need. Brain cells
also
need imagination to some extent, no matter how much fat we eat.
Red blood cells also need glucose, is it carbonated water? It's
glucose that gives them
normal function.
No matter how good you are, no matter
how well our body uses key turns, it
seems like that.  There are tissues that absolutely need glucose.
These tissues use the glucose produced through
reconstitution and genesis glucose
synthesis
as fuel when a person with poor health eats.
When Todd and reconstitution are combined to
create such a port, our
bodies are eating a meal that they can't eat. If we're experiencing this
for a long time, whether it's
with our bodies or
not, and we know that Samsung won't come in for the next long 2, and that the cold 3 won't
come in anyway, we
can use glucose in the same way. We
can use other glucose sources, but ketones can also use glucose.
For example, muscles and the largest
glucose storage and fixation muscles in the body.
I just want to grow taller. I
'm a pod. Now, they adapt and change in this way. They
don't accept the note sugar
because they
know they won't eat the sugar in the 2 anyway. So, wouldn't it be
more efficient to give the sugar our bodies make to those who need it? Like
the cells in the universe or the
red blood cells. So, we
completely eliminate the channel through which the muscles accept glucose. It's called the blue transpo
channel.  The crucible
channel,
literally the pathway that receives the allowance, is
completely destroyed in that step, and
the muscles cannot accept glucose,
and when we eat the reward, it
can no longer be used as energy. Except for the
small amount of glucose produced in our body,
that
small amount of glucose goes to red blood cells and
the like, and our body
cannot process the glucose stored in other places.
Now, this is, so to speak, a physiological
state that was intentionally created this year, and it is a
state of renal failure. It is
a bit strange to say that the four branches in the middle
are different, but anyway, you can
think of it as this state. The
advantage that we intentionally created is sincerity.
But if that state is
one person and you
start eating again, it
will be resolved after three days. It will
be resolved quickly. The exploration robot.
After about three days, the muscles
will start to produce more fat and absorb it again.
So if you just eat consistently, it
will return to normal, so you
don't have to eat a ladle.
But in that sense,
rather than eating too much of a poor life this year, I
recommend that you eat exploration water once in a while.  They
also say that it's better.
Ma, hello.
Where did you go? I'm
going. I have to
go to the bathroom twice while sleeping at night. It's
been over two months since I've had some free time. Summary:
What's the biggest cause of gardening?
Hello, Mr. Bang.
First of all, if it suddenly happened while dieting, there's
no chance of it being a cell thought.
When the sun is dumping, less comes, so it has to
keep expelling it.
The heart keeps storing it, and the kidneys
can't bear the burden. Now, the bladder is storing it.
This is a huge burden on the body,
so it
keeps pouring down through the kidneys, so
somehow it has to be
expended quickly. There are a
lot of English and bread 6 pterosaurs and things like that. It
might mean a little more when
you set up a mock-up. Or, if you drink some water before going to bed,
use 1-1 teaspoon of salt before going to bed.
If you eat this together, the salt
produces an antidiuretic hormone.
As the name suggests, an antidiuretic hormone prevents our body from
producing urine. It's a hormone that prevents urine from being
produced.
So now, that ramen.  If you eat and sleep, you'll wake up the
next morning swollen. There
are also burnt foods and more.
Salt prevents you from completing the first plate,
and carbohydrates
trigger an insulin spike, especially
at night. If you wake up with an insulin spike, your
blood sugar level won't drop well. Oh, and as I
mentioned earlier, you have insulin at night,
so the
kidneys retain more water and the
antidiuretic hormone. The antidiuretic hormone caused by salt
also
prevents you from smoking. When
these factors overlap, our bodies
retain water, which is why our faces are swollen.
Similarly, you can use this to your advantage. If you
eat some salt and
go to bed, you
can go to the bathroom less often.
Study the 7th article of Lucos. Insulin levels
vary depending on age. Glocose is not only blood sugar
but also blood sugar levels. My current
blood sugar level is
how much sugar I have,
and fasting insulin is
how much insulin I have,
so you can
look at them as completely different numbers.
Even if my blood sugar is normal, it's
92, so I usually
sleep with that level. But that's not the case.  Meanwhile, insulin
may be released at levels of 13, 15, and 10.
Insulin is being released like crazy and is
lowering the fasting blood sugar level somehow.
Yes, if you look at it now, you
can think of it as being on the verge of developing diabetes. Our body is continuously
pumping out a lot of insulin and
is somehow controlling the blood sugar level, but if this continues a little longer, it
will eventually reach 1. No
matter how much lean is released, it will
reach a point where it can no longer control the blood sugar level. If we
only look at the sugar level that we will study, is this because
I am using a lot of insulin to
control this blood sugar level,
or is it a state where it
can easily control this level even if insulin is hardly released? It has
not even been 9 minutes.
So,
judging diabetes risk based solely on blood sugar levels is
not possible unless the person already has diabetes. This is not there. * It's probably worse than sterilizing it anyway because the heat
has been there for that long.
10 I don't know what to do with it, but I have a
dream. If you
have a building or a kimchi stew, you can give it to the dog.
Oh, washing your face and taking a shower could also be a solution.
Many people are talking about
the neck. I have
n't seen anything like it, but I've been taking medicine for a long time.
uh
Other than that, it
's mostly fat and cholesterol.
And it
contains a lot of nutrients like serine phosphodiesterase, which can help our nervous system and cell membranes regenerate.
There's also a lot of vitamin D. Compared to other regular lean meats,
this is a grain of
salt. You
have to request insulin separately.
Now,
the internal medicine department, so the test results
were 90 degrees Celsius. The basic test was
n't that great, so they
provided it here. They said that since the fasting blood sugar level
was okay, there's no diabetes.
Now, just now  As I said,
even if your fasting blood sugar is okay, this Julie
might be coming out like crazy right now, so it's
better to look at it separately. I'm
not confident in the author.
1 cup - This really needs to be boiled thoroughly. I'm
not confident in
cutting it. If you eat it whole like this, you won't be able to chew it in your mouth. I just pierced it and swallowed it, so you
have to eat it, but
put it in your mouth and
2. I
talked too much while moving at that time. I
grabbed it roughly with my hand and tore it. I bowed so that it
wouldn't be visible on the screen. It's a bit of a mess before the
twist open Old Testament. 3. It
seems you can use it to make you want to go back to your hometown. It
seems like it would be a good idea to use it to put it to sleep. I've
never eaten a cool, superficial formation on top of something like a persimmon.
2.
First of all, this is probably called the thymus for young children.
Maybe it's also
called "enough" in
Korean. It's a different word, but it came to mind.
C. Fred, right? P. Fred
has a male voice, but let's meet Choi Jeong. Choi Jeong is a
good-natured S2 player. 3.
* I'll talk about this easily because I've eaten a lot of the skin now.
* Thyroid gland  I had a resection surgery and am
taking thyroid hormone medication. Since it is an area that
sells frozen and dried thyroid hormones, I
ordered it this time. Is
it okay to eat it like the vice president?
Well, the
thyroid gland
contains thyroid hormones.
So if you take hormone medication and
also take thyroid supplements, you may have excessive thyroid hormones.
That is why it would be
good to take it after the lecture on love. You
may need to adjust the dosage.
If you are
taking freeze-dried nutritional supplements regularly, you
can take them instead of the medicine.
In that way, since
thyroid hormones
are contained in it, if you
take them while taking hormone medication,
Isul will hug you a little.
Or, if you are
not able to convert MOT at all,
T3 is activated. If you
are taking frozen thyroid hormones, the
T4 may be
converted to reverse T3,
which may reduce the effectiveness of the medication. It would
be better to take it while monitoring your condition. If it
is more than mitochondria in the ground, it is supposed
to be eaten.
Next, there is a shortage of complex building materials. I
need to buy the items next.
Alpha Keto
and Ballet Light were listed very high. I
don't know what Maki is.
Anyway,
Taemin has used it a lot to metabolize 4 mitochondria's energy.
In a state where it is usually deficient, it is difficult to digest food alone.
In a state where there is chronic gallstones, it is
difficult.
So it is
better to take it in the form of FT with some purpose. 5 It is
not good to take oil for a long time. I
think that antibacterial things like that are only taken temporarily, not for long-term use. Do you
run a ranch at home?
My family has nothing to do with wood, but
I have existing products such as phosphorus, etc. I
just certified them. Anyway, I
am now working at a wood farm run by someone else and raising my animals. The
meat here is very chewy. It
would be good to boil it a little before eating it, but since they are
children who swung the bookshelf,
I can see that the raw milk is increasing a little quickly.
What kind of raw milk are you talking about?
8 Energy
or otherwise,
make yogurt and filter the
yogurt made with whey.  I've
made cream cheese and stuff. I
think it's better to eat it with a little more. You
don't need 02 separately to make the cloudy inside. The
cream floats on the top of the raw milk Navi 2. You
can use that to collect the scent. As for the water, you have to
pour it here, but it's a bit of a hassle to use it like that. I've
just been busy with milk, so I
haven't tried it yet. I was
thinking about making butter, but we had a lot of people left over last Chuseok and couldn't travel for a long time. I thought about making butter then, but I
left like this, so I didn't make it.
The next day
[music] You
need water and sugar to break down alcohol,
so if you
drink some water and sugar, it will help you with your homework. In simple terms, give it honey water. People who are having a hard time with treatment usually drink honey water. That's why it's called honey water. When you drink alcohol, your body
loses a lot of fat, so I do
n't think you need to take electrolyte supplements.
Drinking some Goro Steiner sparkling water
will help a lot.
You're good with meat and stuff.
Oh, ning.  Star Mineral is this um ah
um Iksan and Pusan
are the only two that contain Pusan ​​and Pusan? M Iksa
is full Gusang
Dimac cheap 893 If you make it,
I think it would be good to try it.
Hello, Jeongchan. I
think I saw it a long time ago when Baek Jong-won went to eat rabbit on Street Fighter or something, but I can't remember well. By the way, is
this really not as tasty as the foreign ones? They say it's because of the
low fat content,
but
there are similar fat contents in Korea.
If you do all the Senda de Jation, most of them will be around 3.5. Anyway, since it's all foreign, the
meat of that year is also foreign in its own way. You can't
generalize all foreign countries,
since there are more than one or two countries.
Now, of course, there are more delicious cucumbers.
Milk is the most representative in terms of fat content, and
regardless of where it's from,
except for the average All-Star, milk from all other cows
is higher than Holstein milk. Anyway,
All-Star now
tastes better, but it sacrifices direction and
quantity.  Because it's a strain that's been sterilized, if you
drink milk that's not imported from abroad
or
just milk with a higher fat content, you
might find it more delicious. I haven't tried many commercially available milks since I've
heard of them being sterilized overseas, but
when I tried them in the US, I
didn't really feel much of a difference.
Among the cucumbers from Korea and regular standby, I thought Pastel O2 was
the most delicious. I
think it was just about the same.
In Ireland, I
remember the Irish ones being a bit tastier, but
now that they've added pros and height, it's
a bit difficult to compare. Is it a free-
range coincidence?
I know it's meaningless to brush past Plus, but I've been having cancer screenings for a while
now, and I'm not eating 1 l, 2 l, 3 7
herbal medicine amounts. It's a
wide range of things to do. It's over 100, so I
'm dying, but I'm not eating the weaknesses. I'm
eating a lot of food and my condition is getting
better. Since I'm using Plus, my German and
English neutral fat is always low, and
there were many notices and HDL.  If you say you do
n't have to worry about it,
that means you have
no HD, low triglycerides, and low
LDL, and there's
no evidence whatsoever that you get cardiovascular disease. There
really isn't any.
And there's absolutely no evidence that LDL itself
causes cardiovascular disease. It's just
talk without any funding.
That's the real basis for the rights industry.
Ah, if you just
carry around the survey results, there's no such thing as observational
research results.
Hello, Jeong-cheon Lee.
Almost 4 things like this aren't that great. I
still have to try that internal ringer again.
Yes, when I ate that fat, there wasn't
really any bad smell or anything. I think you can
think of it as having a slightly stronger scent than the duck.
Um, Iksan Full Busan 100% cotton,
look again. 2
Goegi Now, it even pulls out heavy metals from our bodies, including binding.
2e Fullback Cube
Um,
rather than saying it's extracted from plants, the
plants break it down and it stays
black in the bladder for a long time.  If you wash it, it's a little bit of coal. Think of it as the existing stage. You can
think of it as something like that.
It determines what kind of branched plant it is.
4 It's digging up a job that decomposed a long time ago
underground. It's not a living bride. You
can think of it as something that decomposed underground a long time ago.
Since it's an All-Star, it must have been very salty.
Most of the songs that were added from abroad are just All-Stars.
Kalia Park * Church 0 It's
really ironic. Ah, the fact that free-range,
pasteurized milk from abroad is
more expensive than regular milk in our country means that I've been working
hard to gather and eat almost all of the necks that don't even cover labor
costs. If the nerf had ripened, society would have come out easily. Not even that, but please bring it later and say what? e 2 [Music] 222 4 But there is this. Uh, isn't it? Now, let's match it with toilet paper and don't do beads.
Let's buy a racket messaging camera without dropping it. It seems like it'll be hard for a rabbit to take a camera with toilet paper. I don't ride a carriage with this science. Also, please recommend a supplement that doesn't exist.
Ah,
h. Seal. The most representative and this
issue.  There are many cases where it is lacking, so
try it today.
If you feel like you have trouble digesting fat,
try Oxby.
For example, it is a 33-year-old woman who took it from a cow. It is a
brown-colored
vice president of the bile department. And
if you have overall poor digestion, it
can be due to late-onset
amines. 2. It is something like allithiamine in tape form. HCL and stomach acid supplements. Uh, there are also things that have all the simple elements in one place, but I wonder if it is really necessary. 2. 2. Ex. Bar 155 x is now a cow. I
will bring a little more each.
The pressure is released for a longer time than expected.
Vitamin E is good for the body, and is it essential for the body?
When our body functions as an antioxidant, vitamins are not present.
Now, when
inflammation occurs, it is
necessary to break the cycle of inflammation.
Vitamin E is easily received. When
inflammation occurs in our body, the age-related
reaction continues. Next time, around the
next time, the next inflammation occurs like this.  It's
easy to eat,
but 100t. If we talk about antioxidants, let's say
vitamin E. But now,
there are antioxidants that prevent inflammation from occurring in the first place.
Then, when inflammation occurs, there are
always ones that help to finish it off well in the middle.
Now, think of vitamin
E as a
key role that solves the problem in the middle when it has already occurred. It is
definitely necessary to break the cycle of inflammation.
There are many other roles that come together, but
other vitamins themselves are
not only vitamin E, but also other vitamins like AD Kate. The
soluble vitamins are
not ones that only play a single role, but there are
many different ones. I don't know them all. It's
okay to eat something that is cold-pressed with whole oil or use it in cooking.
What is good for strength training? I've
been in the pickling era for about 20 days now, but it's my
first time eating this much protein, so I feel uneasy and
feel like I should throw it away because I'm wet often.
When I ordered this meat, haha.
Exercise uses protein.  It
's a bit vague, but anyway, for
strength training, of course, just
do one thing.
If you want to keep it simple, it
's better to do compound resistance training. It
doesn't use only the ohm muscles. For example,
barbell curls
don't use these two, right?
Rather than focusing on one muscle, I recommend doing exercises that
use all five muscles together. To
put it simply, the three major exercises are: 5-arm presses, 5-arm presses, and then deadlifts and chin-ups. Opal specs are also good. If you
keep it simple, you can get zinc and
selenium just by eating meat.
In particular, zinc is
already abundant in meat, so
adding 4 or something else doesn't really make sense. Do you
not like the growth rate that children say is not good? Are
there people who have problems with their teeth? When
I eat meat, my head
feels heavy and full of pressure.
3. It's because heat comes to the head a lot.
Well, the elements are
particularly suitable for certain periods of time, such as ring gear.  I do
n't think it's that invasive.
So,
unless you have an allergy, it's
incredibly rare for someone to have an allergy in the early stages.
Of course, it's not impossible, but it's
unlikely for only 4 m. No matter how rare
people
say Jacques Key is, it's rare.
Of course,
there's no guarantee that it won't happen even if both are high-temperature, but I
think it's safe to say that it doesn't happen often.
Houki:
When you eat them together using the same cooking method, is it only Western food that causes this?
If that's true,
it's better to have something other than Hongki.
There are doctors who say that poultry is better for the body than beef.
Dr. Georgia Eid said that she
likes poultry more than raw meat, so she
eats poultry. It's
not completely unheard of.
And there is something like that. I don't
remember exactly if the student was 6,
but it's probably the dishes. If
you eat it for students, you
'll contract it. Then, you'll have an allergic reaction or something like
that. Parasites.  It's not a parasite,
but a tick. I don't remember the origin of the bite. Did the tick
inject a pathogen or a worm?
Anyway, after being bitten by a tick, you feel
unwell after eating meat. I
don't know if it exists in Korea.
Yes, it's
different for each person when it comes to fire, pottery, and water. Since the first part is different, it's
a bit like that. Even if it's
moss, it's said that the
sound is different for each person, so I'm
not sure about it for making hair grow faster.
Yes, pepper division
should occur quickly, but I
saw that. It seems that the fragrance of seaweed, which promotes aging,
promotes hair growth, so it might be a bit different.
Vitamin A is necessary for cell differentiation,
so if you consume more vitamin A, your
hair might grow faster.
But I don't think there's much of a difference.
Scars are bad.
Scars and wounds don't heal well because there's a
lack of collagen,
collagen synthesis isn't working properly in the body, there's a lack of
nutrients needed for collagen synthesis, and there's a
lack of vitamin A.
That can happen,
but the music in that food is
a bit too much.  It looks better if you eat
it.
Hey, it's okay. I'll bring it. Um,
uh, towel, thinking skills. Hello. uh, when you can't eat, there's no need to keep teaching you bad things. Abbott, that example, fire food.
The reason I don't believe that is because
now, what kind of meat is
right for someone and who isn't?
We can have peaceful massages because we can live in the 21st century in Korea. I
think I've said this about 100 times on TV. Ah,
so if you
look at it as a normal human living in a natural state, we are
living an incredibly splendid life in civilization, but if you think about it, for most of human history,
we lived like wild animals outside of the wild, so
open it wide and v2,
most of history, right?
Then, you
have to eat what you catch from hunting, right?
And
when you eat that, you don't
eat it all together.
No, vegetables
don't go well together, so you have to
catch the animals separately.
That kind of thing does
n't make sense. No matter
which group you go to, the traditional group. Dr. Western
Pais looked at any
group. They
all eat the same food. Some people eat the same food. What kind of constitution is it?
There's no such thing as "what kind of constitution do you have?" Currently, that does
n't automatically prove that you don't have a constitution or a certain type of stomach, but
on the other hand, it's a
healthy dog's natural state even if you don't worry about it and eat,
and that's the natural
state of a human being.
At the time of the outbreak, I usually
eat late. Yes, I tend to eat late when I'm broadcasting, but I
don't usually eat this late. And I don't wake up in the morning and finish my meal. Now, I just eat it at lunchtime. I
don't really eat anything like that.
He's breast meat. It's
almost breast meat, and it's a
little big. It's chicken thigh meat.
It's similar to rice in texture, but
rather than being chewy or something, the walls are
chewy, and the
color itself is dark, which
is the color of the reel.
Lee Bolers Maca Sure Ganda.
I don't know enough to say this or that about things like this. You have to know. It
's like that,
right? What was the term? I
can't remember now that you've mentioned it. It's
about tailoring my body to my talents depending on the situation.
For example, if my body
is in a state of fire, it replenishes water energy, and if it
is in a state of water-like energy, it feels
sorry to replenish fire energy. I do
n't know how effective eye contact lenses are because I haven't studied them separately. I do
n't think it's necessary to eat 4 conspiracies.
That's the reason I studied them.
Including specific food plants that only grow in certain regions. Special
products that can only be obtained in certain regions were truly only available in those regions. Since
humans have
lived in all regions, from the polar regions to 12:30, regardless of whether they are from the past or present,
if there is a specific plant found in a tropical
region, for
example,
there are superfoods found in the tropical rainforests of Southeast Asia across Africa and South America.
Of course, they can be good for the body, but we have to
eat superfoods that can only be eaten in
Southeast Asia.
If that weren't the case, then there would be
foods that are abundant everywhere, of course, which
can be good for the body, but I do
n't think they are essential anymore.
I also
have keloids, keloid skin, and that
kind of thing here.  This isn't a wound,
but rather a surgical procedure.
Like here, other injuries to the body
leave long-lasting scars.
And the swelling is gone. After
getting the treatment, it's almost completely
gone.
Yes, it was fake, but it was so bad that it felt like my whole body was
shattered, like the bones on the back of my hand were torn like this. It was
weird, but it was there. So, my brother and I
came out a little bigger, and this part
wasn't in good shape, but
after I changed it, it was fine.
This person only has a silver wound. He does
n't seem to get hurt easily.
He also gets wounds really easily.
While working on the ranch, I do this kind of
thing all the time, so I have
a lot of scars on my body. They
keep
appearing, but they quickly disappear, and I think, "
Oh, I know it'll heal." I
don't care about blue, and I just keep getting torn,
scratched, cut, and all
that.
But when I suddenly think about it, it tastes good. Oh, but when I dumped oxalic acid, it started to
itch and sting a lot here.
Food can also make your head spin. It seems
like he's
getting the nutrients our brain needs.  Eating is
much better than eating myself. It's
a little bit of a headache.
4th generation is quiet.
8.
Don't you use detergent, laundry detergent, or fabric softener? I
went to see the daily chemical products store, but I
wonder what detergents I should use. I don't use the original detergent. I
just use the detergent for beggar use.
[Music] I
don't wash dishes well anymore. I don't use the
raw detergent
often. When I have to clean something that's extremely greasy after a long time, I do
n't use the 3rd one. I
don't do it in depth on purpose, but I
didn't wash the dishes well. Even
when I wash the dishes, I often just use water.
Accessories like these should be as simple as possible.
If you use a lot of the properties that open them, it
'll work. In fact,
the purpose is to
remove grease. If you change it to simple things, I think you'll understand better. Use something that doesn't contain bread or things like that. Betaine phosphate, betaine phosphate. That's something insert. Sister, protease. SCD active protease. It's a protein-digesting enzyme supplement.
It's similar. I do
n't know what the food is.
Yes, so I don't know how effective it will be,
but
if you feel like you're having trouble digesting protein, it can be buried. Since
active protease is
literally activated when this acid is well produced, you should also
pay attention to whether you have insufficient stomach acid.
If you eat less fat and
are lacking calories, your
hair will grow slowly. If you
have a lot of other things to take in, it's
difficult to focus on hair growth. HCL is not a
thought of others. It
's more than Thai salt. H seed, right?
OS CD Active Protease Blend.
It's a mixture of various things. A
mixture of taxol might be more helpful.
H seed's alone. Betaine
HCL.
You can also take something that only contains this.
4. Since pediatric elements are
said to not cause any side effects or anything if you take a lot, I
think you can try it. I
don't recommend taking a lot of the supplement itself, but
I want to try it, but my hair is
long, so I can't even think about
shampoo bars.  I'm thinking of making and using it.
2. I doubt it's successful. I'll post it on the cafe. It's
young and
long, and then it
doesn't really have anything to do with having long
hair, right? Of course, I didn't have any
hair and I'm bald. It came out as a can prosthesis. Same as 1. When you have hair
like mine or have long hair, it does
n't mean that the hair that grows long like this secretes something,
right? The
information comes from the scalp, and it's
not like the long hair spits it out from the tip.
What kind of spinning make-up is sticking out its tongue?
Apple's dubbing is also okay. If you
drink it too often, your teeth might
become 10. Just be careful about that.
3:00 9 It would be
good to mix it with something like water. It's
almost like a tongue.
Ah,
it's a really good, high-quality oil. It's
a bit expensive, but it tastes good.
Yes, the scalp is sticking out, so whether
we have short or long scalps, it
doesn't matter at all.
The hair on that side is
hard to wash, and this is now charcoal-steamed.  It's a
matter of quantity. Just because
my hair is this long does
n't mean my scalp is this bad or anything.
Oh, and before I started using Nop, I
first adapted to the egg yolk shampoo. I started using the
right product little by little and gradually reduced the
frequency of shampooing while looking all over the world, and it seemed to
be comparable.
Rather than quitting all at once, I think it would be helpful to gradually do it in small steps with a preview lens. I
like the Roland shampoo tag. It
gives you a lot of stamina and gives you a lot of stamina. You can eat it quickly. Why are you doing
that? You
can eat SRP any time. You're
trying to eat that acetic acid.
Just enjoy
it. I think you have to push it like this with the same bone. Play. Yes, then let's give clay. Some people wash with col. There are many people who take it. The hampo is as good as the yolk. The cleansing power is also good, but it's a bit too good for the financial aspect. I like the idea so much that during the semester, it
feels like my hair is getting rid of too much oil, so it seems like it's like this.
When I draw, it's bot 3 for a year,
and about Samsung 3 parts.
2. It
has all the good things.  It
has Biotherm in it, it's slightly acidic, and the
3 barriers are good,
uh uh 2
Oxalic acid dumping
can pass by almost without noticing it depending on what I've been eating.
2 You
may experience some extreme symptoms
* There are many people who started not eating acid and
recovered in more than a week.
2 It
doesn't take that long. First, it takes time to start dumping,
but now our body,
for example, vitamin P sex navigator
deficiency is too severe, and if there are
too many bosses who produce it themselves, even if you
stop copying silver, you
may not be able to start the homepage, but
that doesn't happen often when Khan is playing ball.
uh
uh The yolk is in
good condition.
If your head gets stuck, it can go up a bit to use one silver.
Then, if you
eat three dumplings, he said that hair that reaches your shoulders is
one. If
you grow it higher than your shoulders, it
would be better to use about two silver.
2 It's
almost always eaten as a boiled dish, so it
doesn't have this special taste.
Hmm, it's delicious, but it's like something.
This kind of taste isn't something like this in the world.  It's the
same, and the
shaking part is delicious, and the
skin is chewy and
restrained, so it
's really good. Ahhh, it's not lunch. Tomorrow, the first dog book, Sannim, said that his family will come over to visit, so I want to let the clothes out to pasture. So, I don't know if it will work out well, but
for the sake of the last time we caught it,
Vivian, you
assembled the milking machine for me.
At that time, you
said that you were missing a few parts,
but because there were so few parts, I
couldn't finish assembling it.
I was
embarrassed, but I just let it be until now.
So, I gave it to you, and I just left it as it was.
Yes, I
finished building the house that I'll put on top. I'll show you. It
was a little shabby at the time, but it's
a little more presentable than the Cora teapot, but
this is it.
Ah,
Expo. I really worked hard on this.
Also, it
was a bit steep, so it was
n't easy because I knew how to put rice on the legs. Anyway, it's all finished now, so I just need to
put it carefully. Here, I forgot to
make it when I was milking. Anyway, I think I
can put it up once I have a decent machine.  I
came here to finish writing the article on the machine I was using, and I didn't know
what to do because the parts were really missing.
So, I
temporarily went to a hardware store and
put together a few things that seemed like they would work. I'll test run it tomorrow, and
if it goes well, I'll be able to upload the silver cow right away. It
shouldn't be an enemy 1. If
we can
just make it an Olympic ally, I think I've achieved my goal for this year to some extent, so I
hope I can finish the method well.
Egg, we almost have something in common, but
after cutting off and receiving from them at that time or something, the kids' mental state has deteriorated and they're on a
hunger strike for the 1st and 1st time due to trauma. They were already very skinny, but they were
n't given much even if they were alive, so
please hurry up and manage the remaining feed. I fed them all to Cain and disposed of them, and if they
fell, I was
going to slaughter them.
But they
won't eat. Now, they're
traumatized and my
son has depression and is
still insisting.
So, I ate and,
at the last minute, I overcame the
trauma and
ate all the remaining food to
live again.  I
don't know because I don't think I'll have enough time to wait until they're all done. Should I just
post something like "Free Giveaway" on Naver Cafe?
There are cafes that
run like this. Do you think it's a big deal? If I post "
Free Giveaway," someone will come and get it. I wonder if I should do that. It takes a long time and it's hard, but if I catch them like this, they're already weak, and if I keep starving them like this, they'll only be able to answer. I should wrap up the broadcast and
clean up this morning. I
didn't hear that MSC was coming, but
thank you for watching today. Please
press once and the
crime will be broadcast again. Oh,
and I wonder if that kid will be cut off because he said this at the end these days. The
broadcast has
a lot of interesting stories about the coronavirus vaccine and information
on the Doctor's Channel on Christmas morning.
I'd like to talk about that more later.
As
expected, I knew it was a scam, but I
didn't think it would be that useless. Come
on, I'll
see you for the tenth time. Thank you for the review.